Guide to the Robert Fridenberg Collection of Portrait and Topographical Prints
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Portraits, Series I
  - C
    - Cond - Cree general, 9 (Box 36, Folder 548-556)
    - Crel - Cz general, 5 (Box 37, Folder 557-561)
    - Cable, George Washington, 1844-1925 (Box 38, Folder 562)
    - Cabot, Sebastian, ca.1474-1557 (Box 38, Folder 563)
    - Cadoudal, Georges, 1771-1804 (Box 38, Folder 564)
    - Cadwalader (Box 38, Folder 565)
    - Caesar (17th-18th century) (Box 38, Folder 566)
    - Cagliostro, Alessandro, conte di, 1743-1795 (Box 38, Folder 567)
    - Calamy (Box 38, Folder 568)
    - Calas, Jean, 1698-1762 (Box 38, Folder 569)
    - Calhoun, John C. (John Caldwell), 1782-1850 (Box 38, Folder 570)
    - Calonne, Charles Alexandre de, 1734-1802 (Box 38, Folder 571)
    - Calvin, Jean, 1509-1564 (Box 38, Folder 572)
    - Cambacérès, Jean Jacques Régis de, 1753-1824 (Box 38, Folder 573)
    - Cambon, Joseph, 1756-1820 (Box 38, Folder 574)
    - Cambronne, Pierre, 1770-1842 (Box 38, Folder 575)
    - Camden, Charles Pratt, Earl, 1714-1794 (Box 38, Folder 576)
    - Camden, William, 1551-1623 (Box 38, Folder 577)
    - Camões, Luís de, 1524?-1580 (Box 38, Folder 578)
    - Campbell (Box 38, Folder 579)
    - Campbell, Thomas (Box 38, Folder 580)
    - Camus, Armand-Gaston, 1740-1804 (Box 38, Folder 581)
    - Canning, Charles John, Earl Canning, 1812-1862 (Box 38, Folder 582)
    - Canning, George, 1770-1827 (Box 38, Folder 583)
    - Cannon (Box 38, Folder 584)
    - Capel of Hadham, Arthur Capel, Baron, 1610?-1649 (Box 39, Folder 585)
    - Capellen (Box 39, Folder 586)
    - Carew, Bampfylde Moore, 1693-1770? (Box 39, Folder 587)
    - Carlisle (Box 39, Folder 588)
    - Carlisle, Frederick Howard, Earl of, 1748-1825 (Box 39, Folder 589)
    - Carlyle, Thomas, 1795-1881 (Box 39, Folder 590)
    - Carnot (Box 39, Folder 591)
    - Carnot, Lazare, 1753-1823 (Box 39, Folder 592)
    - Carrel, Armand, 1800-1836 (Box 39, Folder 593)
    - Carrier, Jean-Baptiste, 1756-1794 (Box 39, Folder 594)
    - Cary
    - Casey, Silas, 1807-1882 (Box 39, Folder 595)
    - Cass, Lewis, 1782-1866 (Box 39, Folder 596)
    - Castlereagh, Robert Stewart, Viscount, 1769-1822 (Box 39, Folder 597)
    - Cathelineau, Jacques, 1759-1793 (Box 39, Folder 598)
    - Catinat, Nicolas, 1637-1712 (Box 39, Folder 599)
    - Caulaincourt, Armand-Augustin-Louis de, duc de Vicence, 1773-1827 (Box 39, Folder 600)
    - Caylus, Anne Claude Philippe, comte de, 1692-1765 (Box 39, Folder 601)
    - Cazalès, Jacques-Antoine-Marie de, 1758-1805 (Box 39, Folder 602)
    - Cellini, Benvenuto, 1500-1571 (Box 39, Folder 603)
    - Cenci, Beatrice, 1577-1599 (Box 39, Folder 604)
    - Cervantes Saavedra, Miguel de, 1547-1616 (Box 39, Folder 605)
    - Chambord, Henri-Charles-Ferdinand-Marie-Dieudonné d'Artois, comte de, 1820-1883 (Box 39, Folder 606)
    - Championnet, Jean-Etienne, 1762-1800 (Box 39, Folder 607)
    - Chapman (Box 39, Folder 608)
    - Charette de La Contrie, François-Athanase de, 1763-1796 (Box 40, Folder 609)
    - Charles, Archduke of Austria, 1771-1847 (Box 40, Folder 610)
    - Charles Borromeo, Saint, 1538-1584 (Box 40, Folder 611)
    - Charles, Duke of Burgundy, 1433-1477 (Box 40, Folder 612)
    - Charles Martel, approximately 688-741 (Box 40, Folder 613)
    - Chase, Salmon P. (Salmon Portland), 1808-1873 (Box 40, Folder 614)
    - Chase, Samuel, 1741-1811 (Box 40, Folder 615)
    - Chateaubriand, François-René, vicomte de, 1768-1848 (Box 40, Folder 616)
    - Châteauroux, Marie Anne de Mailly-Nesle, duchesse de, 1717-1744 (Box 40, Folder 617)
    - Chatterton, Thomas, 1752-1770 (Box 40, Folder 618)
    - Chaucer, Geoffrey, d. 1400, 2 (Box 40, Folder 619-620)
    - Chaulieu, Guillaume Amfrye de, 1639-1720 (Box 40, Folder 621)
    - Chénier, André, 1762-1794 (Box 40, Folder 622)
    - Chénier, Marie-Joseph, 1764-1811 (Box 40, Folder 623)
    - Chesterfield (Box 40, Folder 624)
    - Chesterfield, Philip Dormer Stanhope, Earl of, 1694-1773 (Box 40, Folder 625)
    - Chevreuse (Box 40, Folder 626)
    - Chevreuse, Claude de Lorraine, duc de, 1578-1657 (Box 40, Folder 627)
    - Chevert, Francois de (Box 40, Folder 628)
    - Chichele, Henry, 1362?-1443 (Box 40, Folder 629)
    - Choate, Rufus, 1799-1859 (Box 41, Folder 630)
    - Choiseul (Box 41, Folder 631)
    - Choiseul, Etienne-François, duc de, 1719-1785 (Box 41, Folder 632)
    - Churchill, Charles, 1731-1764 (Box 41, Folder 633)
    - Cinq-Mars, Henri Coiffier Ruzé d'Effiat, marquis de, 1620-1642 (Box 41, Folder 634)
    - Clanricarde, Ulick de Burgh, Earl of, 1604-1657 (Box 41, Folder 635)
    - Clapperton, Hugh, 1788-1827 (Box 41, Folder 636)
    - Clare (Box 41, Folder 637)
    - Clarence (Box 41, Folder 638)
    - Clarendon (Box 41, Folder 639)
    - Clarendon, Edward Hyde, Earl of, 1609-1674 (Box 41, Folder 640)
    - Claretie, Jules, 1840-1913 (Box 41, Folder 641)
    - Clark (Box 41, Folder 642)
    - Clarke (Box 41, Folder 643)
    - Clarke, Adam, ca. 1762-1832 (Box 41, Folder 644)
    - Clarke, Edward Daniel, 1769-1822 (Box 41, Folder 645)
    - Clarke, Samuel, 1599-1682 (Box 41, Folder 646)
    - Clarke, Samuel, 1675-1729 (Box 41, Folder 647)
    - Clausel, Bertrand, comte, 1772-1842 (Box 41, Folder 648)
    - Clavière, Étienne, 1735-1793 (Box 41, Folder 649)
    - Clay, Henry, 1777-1852 (Box 41, Folder 650)
    - Clément, Jacques, ca. 1567-1589 (Box 41, Folder 651)
    - Clermont-Tonnerre, Stanislas, comte de, 1747-1792 (Box 41, Folder 652)
    - Cleveland, John, 1613-1658 (Box 41, Folder 653)
    - Clinton, DeWitt, 1769-1828 (Box 41, Folder 654)
    - Clinton, George, 1739-1812 (Box 41, Folder 655)
    - Clinton, Henry, Sir, 1738?-1795 (Box 41, Folder 656)
    - Clive, Robert Clive, Baron, 1725-1774 (Box 42, Folder 657)
    - Clyde, Colin Campbell, Baron, 1792-1863 (Box 42, Folder 658)
    - Clymer, George, 1739-1813 (Box 42, Folder 659)
    - Cobb, James, 1756-1818 (Box 42, Folder 660)
    - Cobbett, William, 1763-1835 (Box 42, Folder 661)
    - Cobden, Richard, 1804-1865 (Box 42, Folder 662)
    - Codrington, Edward, Sir, 1770-1851 (Box 42, Folder 663)
    - Cœur, Jacques, d. 1456 (Box 42, Folder 664)
    - Coëffier de Ruzé d'Effiat, Antoine (Box 42, Folder 665)
    - Coislin (Box 42, Folder 666)
    - Coke, Edward, Sir, 1552-1634 (Box 42, Folder 667)
    - Colardeau, M. (Charles-Pierre), 1732-1776 (Box 42, Folder 668)
    - Colbert (Box 42, Folder 669)
    - Colbert, Jean Baptiste, 1619-1683, 2 (Box 42, Folder 670-671)
    - Coleridge-Taylor, Samuel, 1875-1912 (Box 42, Folder 672)
    - Coletus, Joannes (Box 42, Folder 673)
    - Coligny, Gaspard de, duc de Châtillon, 1584-1649 and Angelique Yzabelle de Montmorency (Box 42, Folder 674)
    - Coligny, Gaspard de, seigneur de Châtillon, 1519-1572 (Box 42, Folder 675)
    - Collier, George, Sir, 1738-1795 (Box 42, Folder 676)
    - Collingwood, Cuthbert Collingwood, Baron, 1750-1810 (Box 42, Folder 677)
    - Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768 (Box 42, Folder 678)
    - Collot d'Herbois, Jean-Marie, 1750-1796 (Box 42, Folder 679)
    - Colman, George, 1732-1794 (Box 42, Folder 680)
    - Columbus, Christopher, 2 (Box 43, Folder 681-682)
    - Commynes, Philippe de, ca. 1447-1511 (Box 43, Folder 683)
    - Concini, Concino, maréchal d'Ancre, ca. 1575-1617 (Box 43, Folder 684)
    - Condé (Box 43, Folder 685)
    - Condé, Louis, prince de, 1621-1686 [le Grand Condé] (Box 43, Folder 686)
    - Condillac, Etienne Bonnot de, 1714-1780 (Box 43, Folder 687)
    - Condorcet, Jean-Antoine-Nicolas de Caritat, marquis de, 1743-1794 (Box 43, Folder 688)
    - Congreve, William, 1670-1729 (Box 43, Folder 689)
    - Conkling, Roscoe, 1829-1888 (Box 43, Folder 690)
    - Contarini (Box 43, Folder 691)
    - Conway, Henry Seymour, 1721-1795 (Box 43, Folder 692)
    - Cook, James, 1728-1779 (Box 43, Folder 693)
    - Cooper, James Fenimore, 1789-1851 (Box 43, Folder 694)
    - Copernicus, Nicolaus, 1473-1543 (Box 43, Folder 695)
    - Coram, Thomas, 1668?-1751 (Box 43, Folder 696)
    - Corbet, Richard, 1582-1635 (Box 43, Folder 697)
    - Corday, Charlotte, 1768-1793 (Box 43, Folder 698)
    - Corneille, Pierre, 1606-1684, 2 (Box 44, Folder 699-700)
    - Corneille, Thomas, 1625-1709 (Box 44, Folder 701)
    - Cornwall, Barry, 1787-1874 (Box 44, Folder 702)
    - Cornwallis, Charles Cornwallis, Marquis, 1738-1805, 2 (Box 44, Folder 703-704)
    - Cortés, Hernán, 1485-1547 (Box 44, Folder 705)
    - Cotin, Charles, 1604-1682 (Box 44, Folder 706)
    - Cottington, Francis Cottington, Baron, 1579?-1652 (Box 44, Folder 707)
    - Cotton, Charles, 1630-1687 (Box 44, Folder 708)
    - Coulanges, Christophe de, 1607-1687 (Box 44, Folder 709)
    - Couthon, Georges Auguste, 1755-1794 (Box 44, Folder 710)
    - Coventry, Thomas Coventry, Baron, 1578-1640 (Box 44, Folder 711)
    - Coverdale, Miles, 1488-1568 (Box 44, Folder 712)
    - Cowley, Abraham, 1618-1667 (Box 44, Folder 713)
    - Cowper (Box 44, Folder 714)
    - Cowper, William, 1731-1800 [and mother] (Box 44, Folder 715)
    - Crabbe, George, 1754-1832 (Box 44, Folder 716)
    - Cranmer, Thomas, 1489-1556 (Box 45, Folder 717)
    - Craven, William Craven, Earl of, 1606-1697 (Box 45, Folder 718)
    - Crébillon, Claude-Prosper Jolyot de, 1707-1777, 2 (Box 45, Folder 719-720)
    - Créquy (Box 45, Folder 721)
    - Crichton, James, 1560-1582 (Box 45, Folder 722)
    - Crillon, Louis des Balbes de Berton de, 1541-1615 (Box 45, Folder 723)
    - Crittenden (Box 45, Folder 724)
    - Croker, John Wilson, 1780-1857 (Box 45, Folder 725)
    - Cromwell, Henry, 1628-1674 (Box 45, Folder 726)
    - Cromwell, Oliver, 1599-1658 (Box 45, Folder 727)
    - Cromwell, Richard, 1626-1712 (Box 45, Folder 728)
    - Cromwell, Thomas, Earl of Essex, 1485?-1540 (Box 45, Folder 729)
    - Cruden, Alexander, 1699-1770 (Box 45, Folder 730)
    - Cujas, Jacques, 1522-1590 (Box 45, Folder 731)
    - Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654 (Box 45, Folder 732)
    - Cumberland, George Clifford, Earl of, 1558-1605, and Anne Clifford (Box 45, Folder 733)
    - Cumberland, Richard, 1732-1811 (Box 45, Folder 734)
    - Cunningham, Allan, 1784-1842 (Box 45, Folder 735)
    - Curran, John P. (John Philpot), b. 1870 (Box 45, Folder 736)
    - Curtis, George William, 1824-1892 (Box 45, Folder 737)
    - Curtis, Roger, Sir, 1746-1816 (Box 45, Folder 738)
    - Cushing, Caleb, 1800-1879 (Box 45, Folder 739)
    - Custine, Adam Philippe, comte de, 1740-1793 (Box 45, Folder 740)
    - Oversize
      - Ca - Car general, 10 (Box 46 (Oversize), Folder 741-750)
      - Carr - Chamb general, 8 (Box 47 (Oversize), Folder 751-758)
      - Chami - Clap general, 10 (Box 48 (Oversize), Folder 759-768)
      - Clar - Cour general, 10 (Box 49 (Oversize), Folder 769-778)
      - Cous - Cz general, 5 (Box 50 (Oversize), Folder 779-783)
      - Cable - Carlisle, 23 (Box 51 (Oversize), Folder 784-806)
      - Carlyle - Chevert, 30 (Box 52 (Oversize), Folder 807-836)
      - Chichele - Coke, 33 (Box 53 (Oversize), Folder 837-869)
      - Colbert - Crabbe, 31 (Box 54 (Oversize), Folder 870-900)
      - Cranmer - Custine, 16 (Box 55 (Oversize), Folder 901-916)
  - D
    - Da - Desm general, 6 (Box 56, Folder 917-922)
    - Desn - Dume general, 6 (Box 57, Folder 923-928)
    - Dumo - Dz general, 5 (Box 58, Folder 929-933)
    - Dalyell, Thomas 1599?-1685 (Box 59, Folder 934)
    - Dampierre (Box 59, Folder 935)
    - Dana, Richard Henry, 1815-1882 (Box 59, Folder 936)
    - Danby, Henry Danvers, Earl of, 1573-1644 (Box 59, Folder 937)
    - Dangeau, Philippe de Courcillon, marquis de, 1638-1720 (Box 59, Folder 938)
    - Daniel (Box 59, Folder 939)
    - Danton, Georges Jacques, 1759-1794 (Box 59, Folder 940)
    - Dante Alighieri, 1265-1321 (Box 59, Folder 941)
    - Darnley, Henry Stuart, Lord, 1545-1567 (Box 59, Folder 942)
    - Dartmouth (Box 59, Folder 943)
    - Darwin, Charles, 1809-1882 (Box 59, Folder 944)
    - Daudet, Alphonse, 1840-1897 (Box 59, Folder 945)
    - D'Avenant, William, Sir, 1606-1668 (Box 59, Folder 946)
    - Davenport (Box 59, Folder 947)
    - Davi, Jacques, Cardinal Du Perron 1556-1615 (Box 59, Folder 948)
    - Davis (Box 59, Folder 949)
    - Davout, Louis Nicolas, duc d'Auerstædt et prince d'Eckmühl, 1770-1823 (Box 59, Folder 950)
    - De la Mare, Walter, 1873-1956 (Box 59, Folder 951)
    - De Quincy, Thomas, 1785-1859 (Box 59, Folder 952)
    - Deane, Silas, 1737-1789 (Box 59, Folder 953)
    - Decatur, Stephen (Box 59, Folder 954)
    - Dee, John, 1527-1608 (Box 59, Folder 955)
    - Dekker, Thomas, ca. 1572-1632
    - Defoe, Daniel, 1661?-1731 (Box 59, Folder 956)
    - Delille, Jacques, 1738-1813 (Box 59, Folder 957)
    - Demoustier, C. A. (Charles Albert), 1760-1801 (Box 59, Folder 958)
    - Denham (Box 59, Folder 959)
    - Derby (Box 60, Folder 960)
    - Derby, Edward Henry Stanley, Earl of, 1826-1893 (Box 60, Folder 961)
    - Derby, James Stanley, Earl of, 1607-1651 (Box 60, Folder 962)
    - Desaix, Louis-Charles-Antoine, 1768-1800 (Box 60, Folder 963)
    - Descartes, René, 1596-1650 (Box 60, Folder 964)
    - Desforges-Maillard, M. (Paul), 1699-1772 (Box 60, Folder 965)
    - Deshoulières, Madame (Antoinette), ca. 1634-1694 (Box 60, Folder 966)
    - Desmoulins, Camille, 1760-1794 (Box 60, Folder 967)
    - Destouches, Néricault, 1680-1754 (Box 60, Folder 968)
    - Devonshire (Box 60, Folder 969)
    - Devonshire, Charles Blount, Earl of, 1563-1606 (Box 60, Folder 970)
    - Devonshire, Georgiana Spencer Cavendish, Duchess of, 1757-1806 (Box 60, Folder 971)
    - Devonshire, Spencer Compton Cavendish, Duke of, 1833-1908 (Box 60, Folder 972)
    - Devonshire, William Cavendish, Duke of, 1640-1707 (Box 60, Folder 973)
    - Dibdin (Box 60, Folder 974)
    - Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870 (Box 60, Folder 975)
    - Dickinson, John, 1732-1808 (Box 60, Folder 976)
    - Diderot, Denis, 1713-1784 (Box 60, Folder 977)
    - Digby, Kenelm, 1603-1665 (Box 60, Folder 978)
    - Dillon (Box 60, Folder 979)
    - Disraeli, Benjamin, Earl of Beaconsfield, 1804-1881 (Box 60, Folder 980)
    - Dixon, William Hepworth, 1821-1879 (Box 60, Folder 981)
    - Dodd, William, 1729-1777 (Box 61, Folder 982)
    - Doddridge, Philip, 1702-1751 (Box 61, Folder 983)
    - Donne, John, 1572-1631 (Box 61, Folder 984)
    - Dorat, Claude Joseph, 1734-1780 (Box 61, Folder 985)
    - Dorchester, Guy Carleton, Baron, 1724-1808 (Box 61, Folder 986)
    - Doré, Gustave, 1832-1883 (Box 61, Folder 987)
    - Doria, Andrea, 1466-1560
    - Dorislaus, Isaac, 1595-1649
    - Dorset (Box 61, Folder 988)
    - Dorset, Edward Sackville, Earl of, 1591-1652 (Box 61, Folder 989)
    - Dorset, Thomas Sackville, Earl of, 1536-1608 (Box 61, Folder 990)
    - Douglas (Box 61, Folder 991)
    - Douglas, Stephen A. (Stephen Arnold), 1813-1861 (Box 61, Folder 992)
    - Douglass, Frederick, 1818-1895 (Box 61, Folder 993)
    - Downshire, Wills Hill, Marquis of, 1718-1893 (Box 61, Folder 994)
    - Drake, Francis, Sir, 1540?-1596 (Box 61, Folder 995)
    - Draper, William, Sir, 1721-1787 (Box 61, Folder 996)
    - Dryden, John, 1631-1700 (Box 61, Folder 997)
    - Du Barry, Jeanne Bécu, comtesse, 1743-1793 (Box 61, Folder 998)
    - Ducis, J.-F. (Jean-François), 1733-1816 (Box 61, Folder 999)
    - Dudley (Box 61, Folder 1000)
    - Dufferin and Ava, Frederick Temple Blackwood, Marquis of, 1826-1902 (Box 61, Folder 1001)
    - Du Guay-Trouin, René, 1673-1736 (Box 61, Folder 1002)
    - Dugdale (Box 61, Folder 1003)
    - Du Guesclin, Bertrand, comte de Longueville, ca. 1320-1380 (Box 61, Folder 1004)
    - Dumas, Alexandre, 1802-1870 (Box 61, Folder 1005)
    - Dumesnil, Mlle (Marie-Françoise), 1713-1803 (Box 62, Folder 1006)
    - Dumouriez, Charles François Du Périer, 1739-1823 (Box 62, Folder 1007)
    - Duncan, Isadora, 1877-1927 (Box 62, Folder 1008)
    - Duncan of Camperdown, Adam Duncan, Viscount, 1731-1804 (Box 62, Folder 1009)
    - Dundas (Box 62, Folder 1010)
    - Dunois, Jean, comte de, ca. 1403-1468 (Box 62, Folder 1011)
    - Dupaty, Charles-Marguerite-Jean-Baptiste Mercier, 1746-1788 (Box 62, Folder 1012)
    - Dupont (Box 62, Folder 1013)
    - Du Quesne (Box 62, Folder 1014)
    - Durham (Box 62, Folder 1015)
    - Duroc, Géraud Christophe Michel, duc de Frioul, 1772-1813 (Box 62, Folder 1016)
    - Duval, Alexandre, 1767-1842 (Box 62, Folder 1017)
    - Dwight, Timothy, 1752-1817 (Box 62, Folder 1018)
    - Dyer (Box 62, Folder 1019)
    - Oversize
      - Da - Dou general, 9 (Box 63 (Oversize), Folder 1020-1028)
      - Dow - Dz general, 4 (Box 64 (Oversize), Folder 1029-1032)
      - Daniel - Devonshire, 25 (Box 65 (Oversize), Folder 1033-1057)
      - Dibden - Draper, 20 (Box 66 (Oversize), Folder 1058-1077)
      - Dryden - Dyer, 16 (Box 67 (Oversize), Folder 1078-1093)
  - E
    - Ea - Ez general, 6 (Box 68, Folder 1094-1099)
    - Eads, James Buchanan, 1820-1887 (Box 69, Folder 1100)
    - East, James Buller, Sir, 1789-1878
    - Eastlake, Charles Lock, Sir, 1793-1865
    - Ebers, George (Box 69, Folder 1101)
    - Eccles, Solomon, 1618-1683 (Box 69, Folder 1102)
    - Edgeworth, Honora Sneyd (Box 69, Folder 1103)
    - Edgeworth, Maria, 1767-1849 (Box 69, Folder 1104)
    - Edison, Thomas A. (Thomas Alva), 1847-1931 (Box 69, Folder 1105)
    - Edmonds (Box 69, Folder 1106)
    - Edward, Pfalzgraf von Simmern, 1625-1663
    - Edwards, Jonathan (Box 69, Folder 1107)
    - Edwards, Thomas (all)
    - Edwin, Elizabeth Rebecca, 1771?-1854 (Box 69, Folder 1108)
    - Egan, John (Box 69, Folder 1109)
    - Egerton (Box 69, Folder 1110)
    - Egmond (Box 69, Folder 1111)
    - Egmont (Box 69, Folder 1112)
    - Egon (Box 69, Folder 1113)
    - Egremont, George O'Brien Wyndham, Earl of (Box 69, Folder 1114)
    - Einhard, ca. 770-840 (Box 69, Folder 1115)
    - Elbeuf (Box 69, Folder 1116)
    - Eldon, John Scott, Earl of, 1751-1838 (Box 69, Folder 1117)
    - Elgin, Charles Bruce, Earl of
    - Elgin, James Bruce, Earl of
    - Elgin, Thomas Bruce Earl of
    - Elie de Beaumont, Jean-Baptiste-Jacques, 1732-1786 (Box 69, Folder 1118)
    - Eliot, George, 1819-1880 (Box 69, Folder 1119)
    - Eliot, John, Sir, 1592-1632 (Box 69, Folder 1120)
    - Eliott/Elliot (Box 69, Folder 1121)
    - Ellicott, John Charles 1819-1905 (Box 69, Folder 1122)
    - Elliott, Ebenezer (Box 69, Folder 1123)
    - Elliott, George Augustus (Box 69, Folder 1124)
    - Ellis (Box 69, Folder 1125)
    - Ellison, Cuthbert
    - Ellsworth, Oliver (Box 69, Folder 1126)
    - Emeriau, Maurice-Julien (Box 69, Folder 1127)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo (Box 69, Folder 1128)
    - Emmet, Robert, 1778-1803 (Box 69, Folder 1129)
    - Emory (Box 69, Folder 1130)
    - Endicott (Box 69, Folder 1131)
    - Enghien (Box 69, Folder 1132)
    - Englefield (Box 69, Folder 1133)
    - Eon de Beaumont, Charles Geneviève Louis Auguste André Timothée d', 1728-1810 (Box 69, Folder 1134)
    - Epagny, M. d' (Jean Baptiste), 1787-1868 (Box 69, Folder 1135)
    - Epée, Charles-Michel de l', 1712-1789 (Box 69, Folder 1136)
    - Epernon, Duc d' (Box 69, Folder 1137)
    - Epinay, Louise Florence Pétronille Tardieu d'Esclavelles, marquise d', 1726-1783 (Box 69, Folder 1138)
    - Epo, Boetius, 1529-1599 (Box 69, Folder 1139)
    - Epremenil, Charles Duval d' (Box 69, Folder 1140)
    - Erasmus, Desiderius, d. 1536 (Box 69, Folder 1141)
    - Erckmann, Emile (Box 69, Folder 1142)
    - Ericsson, John, 1803-1889 (Box 69, Folder 1143)
    - Erpingham, Thomas, Sir
    - Erskine (Box 70, Folder 1144)
    - Erving (Box 70, Folder 1145)
    - Escher (Box 70, Folder 1146)
    - Essarts, Pierre de (Box 70, Folder 1147)
    - Essex (Box 70, Folder 1148)
    - Essex, Robert Devereux, Earl of (all) (Box 70, Folder 1149)
    - Essex, Walter Devereux, Earl of, 1541-1576 (Box 70, Folder 1150)
    - Estaing, Charles Henri, Comte d', 1729-1794
    - Este (Box 70, Folder 1151)
    - Esten, Harriet Pye, ca. 1765-1865 (Box 70, Folder 1152)
    - Estrées (Box 70, Folder 1153)
    - Estrées, Gabrielle d' (Box 70, Folder 1154)
    - Espartero, Baldomero, 1793-1879 (Box 70, Folder 1155)
    - Étampes (Box 70, Folder 1156)
    - Étienne, Charles-Guillaume, 1777-1845 (Box 70, Folder 1157)
    - Eu, d' (Box 70, Folder 1158)
    - Eudes (Box 70, Folder 1159)
    - Eugene, of Savoy, Prince of Savoy, 1663-1736 (Box 70, Folder 1160)
    - Euler, Leonhard, 1707-1783. (Box 70, Folder 1161)
    - Eupen, Pieter Jan Simon van, 1744-1804 (Box 70, Folder 1162)
    - Evans, Henry (Box 70, Folder 1163)
    - Evans, John, 1594-1659 (Box 70, Folder 1164)
    - Evans, Robley D., 1846-1912 (Box 70, Folder 1165)
    - Evans, Thomas W., 1823-1897
    - Evarts, William Maxwell, 1818-1901
    - Evelyn, John, 1620-1706 (Box 70, Folder 1166)
    - Everett (Box 70, Folder 1167)
    - Evertsen (Box 70, Folder 1168)
    - Ewell, Richard Stoddert, 1817-1872 (Box 70, Folder 1169)
    - Ewing (Box 70, Folder 1170)
    - Exeter, Elizabeth Cecil, Marchioness of (Box 70, Folder 1171)
    - Exeter, Thomas Cecil, Earl of (Box 70, Folder 1172)
    - Exmouth, Edward Pellew, Viscount, 1757-1833 (Box 70, Folder 1173)
    - Oversize
      - Ea - Ez general, 4 (Box 71 (Oversize), Folder 1174-1177)
      - East - Emmet, 25 (Box 72 (Oversize), Folder 1178-1202)
      - Enghien - Exmouth, 25 (Box 73 (Oversize), Folder 1203-1227)
  - F
    - Fa - Fz general, 7 (Box 74, Folder 1228-1234)
    - Fabert, Abraham de, 1599-1662 (Box 75, Folder 1235)
    - Fabre d'Eglantine, P.-F.-N. (Philippe-François-Nazaire), 1755-1794 (Box 75, Folder 1236)
    - Fairbarn (Box 75, Folder 1237)
    - Fairfax (Box 75, Folder 1238)
    - Fairfax, Thomas Fairfax, Baron, 1612-1671 (Box 75, Folder 1239)
    - Falkland (Box 75, Folder 1240)
    - Falkland, Lucius Cary, Viscount, 1610?-1643 (Box 75, Folder 1241)
    - Farmer, Richard, 1735-1797
    - Fantoni, Giovanni, 1755-1807 (Box 75, Folder 1242)
    - Fanshawe, Richard, 1608-1666 (Box 75, Folder 1243)
    - Faraday, Michael, 1791-1867 (Box 75, Folder 1244)
    - Farnese (Box 75, Folder 1245)
    - Farquhar (Box 75, Folder 1246)
    - Farragut, David Glasgow, 1801-1870 (Box 75, Folder 1247)
    - Farrar (Box 75, Folder 1248)
    - Farrar, F. W. (Frederic William), 1831-1903 (Box 75, Folder 1249)
    - Farrell, Owen, 1716-1742? (Box 75, Folder 1250)
    - Farren
    - Faucher (Box 75, Folder 1251)
    - Fauconberg
    - Faulknor, Robert, 1763-1795 (Box 75, Folder 1252)
    - Faure, Felix (Box 75, Folder 1253)
    - Faustina (Box 75, Folder 1254)
    - Favart, M. (Charles-Simon), 1710-1792 (Box 75, Folder 1255)
    - Favart, Mme (Marie-Justine-Benoîte), 1727-1772 (Box 75, Folder 1256)
    - Favras, Thomas de Mahy, marquis de, 1744-1790 (Box 75, Folder 1257)
    - Fawcett (Box 75, Folder 1258)
    - Fawcett, Henry, 1833-1884 (Box 75, Folder 1259)
    - Fawkes, Guy, 1570-1606 (Box 75, Folder 1260)
    - Feilding, Robert, 1650 or 51-1712 (Box 75, Folder 1261)
    - Feltre, Alphonse-Clarke, Comte de, 1806-1850 (Box 75, Folder 1262)
    - Fenelon, Francois de Salignac de la Mothe, 1651-1715 (Box 75, Folder 1263)
    - Fenton, Elijah, 1683-1730
    - Fenton, Lavinia, 1708-1760 (Box 75, Folder 1264)
    - Ferdinand
    - Ferdinando II, Grand-Duke of Tuscany, 1610-1670 (Box 75, Folder 1265)
    - Ferguson (Box 75, Folder 1266)
    - Ferino, Pierre Marie Barthelemy (Box 75, Folder 1267)
    - Fernández de Córdoba, Gonzalo, 1453-1515 (Box 75, Folder 1268)
    - Ferrara (Box 75, Folder 1269)
    - Fersen (Box 75, Folder 1270)
    - Ferte, La (Box 75, Folder 1271)
    - Fesch, Joseph, 1763-1839 (Box 75, Folder 1272)
    - Fetzer
    - Feuillade, Francois d'Aubusson Duc de La, 1625-1691 (Box 75, Folder 1273)
    - Feuillet, Octave, 1821-1890 (Box 75, Folder 1274)
    - Feval, Paul, 1817-1887
    - Feydeau, Georges
    - Few, William, 1748-1828 (Box 75, Folder 1275)
    - Field, Stephen Johnson, 1816-1899 (Box 76, Folder 1276)
    - Fielding (Box 76, Folder 1277)